Michael mss. LMC 2996
Lilly Library
Michael mss.
1949-2020
Lilly Library
Michael, R. Keith, 1930-
Michael, Marion Bankert
LMC 2996
5 Boxes
The Michael mss., 1949-2020, consist of playbills and theater programs collected by R. Keith and Marion Michael.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift: [2021?]
Arrangement
Programs are arranged alphabetically by play title.
Biographical / Historical
R. Keith and Marion Michael began their careers as professional actors in the early 1950s and began their teaching careers at St. Cloud State College in Minnesota in 1960. In 1971, R. Keith Michael served as the first Chair of the Department of Theatre and Drama at Indiana University, Bloomington; Marion was appointed to IU in 1983. Both professors retired in 1996.
Scope and Contents
The Michael mss., 1949-2020, consist of playbills from plays and theatrical events attended by R. Keith and Marion Michael, professors in the Indiana University Department of Theatre and Drama.
Theater; Indiana University -- Faculty; Michael, R. Keith, 1930-; Michael, Marion Bankert
- Playbills
  - Abigail's Party; Mike Leigh; Ambassador Theatre, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Absence of War; David Hare; Oliver Theatre, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Absurd Person Singular; Alan Ayckbourn; Biltmore Theatre, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accidental Death of an Anarchist; Dario Fo; Wyndham's Theatre, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Acharnians, The; Aristophanes; Herod Atticus Theatre, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advise and Consent; Loring Mandel; Orpheum (Minneapolis), 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Affair, The; Ronald Miller; Henry Miller Theatre, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - After the Revolution; Amy Herzon; TheaterJ DC Jewish CC, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Afterplay; Brian Friel; Studio Theatre, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ages of Man; Queen's Theatre (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agnes of God; Joel Pielmeier; Music Box, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ain't Misbehavin'; Horwitz, Maltby, Waller; Arena Stage (Kreeger), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ain't Too Proud; Dominique Morisseau and The Legendary Motown Catalog; IU Auditorium, 2018 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alarms & Excursions; Michael Frayn; Gielgud Theatre, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - All in the Timing; David Ives; John Housman Theatre, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - All My Sons; Arthur Miller; Cardinal Stage, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - All's Well That Ends Well; William Shakespeare; Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allergist's Wife, The Tale of the; Charles Busch; Ethel Barrymore Theatre, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alone Together; Laurence Roman; Florida Repertory Theatre, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alvin Ailey Dance Theater; Robert Battle (Artistic Dir.); IU Auditorium, 2019 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Amadeus; Peter Shaffer; Oliver Theatre, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - American Idiot, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - And A Nightingale Sang; C.P. Taylor; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Andorra; Max Frisch; Little Theatre Bristol, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Angel Street; Patrick Hamilton; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Angels in America (Pt. 1 & Pt. 2); Tony Kushner; Cottesloe Theatre, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Anna in the Tropics; Nilo Cruz; Royale Theatre, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Anything Goes; Cole Porter; Oliver Theatre, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arguendo; Elevator Repair Service; Wooly Mammoth Theatre Co., 2014 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Art; Yasmina Reza; Wyndham's Theatre, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - As You Like It; William Shakespeare; Theatre Royal Bristol, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - As You Like It [Wie es euch gefällt]; William Shakespeare; Dusseldorf Schauspielhaus, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - As You Like It; William Shakespeare; Barbican Theatre, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - As You Like It; William Shakespeare; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aspern Papers, The; H. James, M. Redgrave; Queen's Theatre, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - August: Osage County; Tracy Letts; Music Box, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Auntie Mame; Lawrence, Lee; Adelphi Theatre, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Avenue Q; Lopez, Marx, Whitty; IU Auditorium, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bacchae; Euripdes; Tom Patterson Theatre, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ballad of the Sad Café, The; Edward Albee; Martin Beck Theatre, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ballet Hispanico; Eduardo Vilaro; IU Auditorium, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Banbury Nose, The; Peter Ustinov; The Playhouse, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Band's Visit, The; D. Yazbek, I. Moses; Ethel Barrymore Theatre, 2019 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barnum; Coleman, Stewart; St. James Theatre, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bartholomew Fair; Ben Jonson; Oliver Theatre, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Beautiful Game, The; Webber, Elton; Cambridge Theatre, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Beauty Queen of Leename, The; Martin McDonagh; Walter Kerr Theatre, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Becket; Jean Anouilh; Stadtheater Wurzburg, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bell, Book and Candle; John Van Druten; Library Theatre, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Benefactors; Michael Frayn; Brooks Atkinson Theatre, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bengal Tiger at the Baghdad Zoo; Rajiv Joseph; Richard Rogers Theatre, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tony Bennett In Concert, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Best Little Whorehouse in Texas; King, Masterson, Hall; 46th Street Theatre, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Betrayal; Harold Pinter; Lyttelton Theatre, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Billy Elliot; Hall, Long; Imperial Theatre, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bingo (Scenes of Money and Death); Edward Bond; Abbey Theatre New York, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Biograph Girl, The; Brown, Heneker; Phoenix Theatre London, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Black Comedy / A Bond Honoured; Shaffer, Osborne; National Theatre, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Blacks, The; Jean Genet; St. Marks Playhouse, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Blast; Mason, James; Murat Centre, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Blithe Spirit [Min fru går igen]; Noel Coward; Lilla Teatern, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Blood Brothers; Willy Russell; Albery Theatre, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bloody Bloody Andrew Jackson; Timbers; Friedman; Bernard B. Jacobs Theatre, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Boeing Boeing; Marc Camoletti; Longacre Theatre, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Blues for Silvia [Un Blues Per Silvia], The; Guido Rocca; Teatro Delle Arti, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ann Bogart: A Mid-Career Celebration, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Book of Mormon, The; Parker, Lopez, Stone; Eugene O'Neill Theatre, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Boris Godunov; Pushkin; Sadrazaj Opere, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Born in the R.S.A.; Barney Simon; Judith Anderson Theatre, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Born Yesterday; Garson Kanin; Festival Theatre (Niagara), 2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Botti, Chris; IU Auditorium, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Boys in the Band, The; Matt Crowley; Wyndham's Theatre, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Breaking the Code; Hugh Whitemore; Neil Simon Theatre, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Breath of Life; David Hare; Theatre Royal Haymarket, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Breath of Spring; Peter Coke; Duke of York's Theatre, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brecht on Brecht; Bertolt Brecht; Theatre de Lys, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brief Encounter; Emma Rice; Studio 54, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brighton Beach Memoirs; Neil Simon; Neil Simon Theatre, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bring in 'Da Noise, Bring in 'Da Funk; Glover and Wolfe; IU Auditorium, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Browing Version & Harlequinade; Terence Rattigan; Lyttleton Theatre, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bubbling Brown Sugar; Loften Mitchell; National Theatre Washington, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Carol Burnett; IU Auditorium, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Business of Murder, The; Richard Harris; Mayfair Theatre, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Butler; Richard Strand; Phoenix Theatre, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bye Bye Birdie; Stewart, Strouse, Adams; Orpheum (Minneapolis), 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cabaret; Masteroff, Kander, Ebb; IU Auditorium, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Camelot; Majestic Theatre, 1961? (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Camille; Pam Gems; Comedy Theatre, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Candida; George Bernard Shaw; Circle in the Square Theatre, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Candida; George Bernard Shaw; Festival Theatre (Niagara), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cantatrice Chauve; Eugene Ionesco; Theatre de la Huchette (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Caretaker, The; Harold Pinter; Lyceum Theatre, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Caretaker, The; Harold Pinter; National Theatre, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Caretaker, The; Harold Pinter; Comedy Theatre, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Carmen; Georges Bizet; Teatro Alla Scala, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Carnival; Merrill, Stewart; Imperial Theatre, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Carousel; Rogers, Hammerstein; Shaftesbury Theatre, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle, The; Bertolt Brecht; Tyrone Guthrie Theatre, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Celestina; Carlo Terron; Buhnen der Stadt Koln, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Changing Room, The; David Storey; Morosco Theatre, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chekhov's Women; Anton Chekhov; Lyric Theatre, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cheri; Anita Loos; National Theatre, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cherry Orchard, The; Anton Chekhov; National Theatre (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cherry Orchard, The; Anton Chekhov; Stratford Festival (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cherry Orchard, The; Anton Chekhov; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cherry Orchard, The; Anton Chekhov; Cottesloe Theatre, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chi La Fa L'Aspetta; Carlo Goldoni; Ridotto dell'Eliseo, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chicago; Fosse, Ebb, Kander; Richard Rogers Theatre, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chicago; Fosse, Ebb, Kander; IU Auditorium, 2018 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Children of a Lesser God; Mark Madoff; Longacre Theatre, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chips with Everything; Arnold Wesker; Plymouth Theatre, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chorus Line, A; Kirkwood, Hamlisch; Shubert Theatre, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chorus of Disapproval, A; Alan Ayckbourn; Oliver Theatre, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Christmas in King Street; Reynolds, Slade; Theatre Royal Bristol, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chrysanthemum; Phillips, Chancellor; Bristol Hippodrome, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Church Basement Ladies 2; Grosch, Curley; Beef & Boards, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Circle, The; W. Somerset Maugham; Ambassador Theatre, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Clandestine Marriage, The; Coleman, Garrick; Nottingham Playhouse, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cleese, John; IU Auditorium, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cleo, Camping, Emmanuelle and Dick; Terry Johnson; Lyttleton Theatre, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cloud 9; Caryl Churchill; Lucille Lortel Theatre, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Color Purple, The; Norman, Russell, Willis, etc.; IU Auditorium, 2020 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Come From Away; Sankoff, Hein; Gerald Schoenfeld, 2018 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Comedians; Trevor Griffiths; Music Box, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Communicating Doors; Alan Ayckbourn; Gielgud Theatre, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Company; Stephen Sondheim; Donmar Warehouse, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Complaisant Lover, The; Graham Green; Globe Theatre Shaftesbury, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Contact; Stroman, Weidman; Vivian Beaumont Theater, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Copenhagen; Michael Frayn; Royale Theatre, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Coriolanus; William Shakespeare; Shakespeare Memorial Theatre, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Coriolanus; William Shakespeare; Festival Theatre (Stratford), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Coriolanus; William Shakespeare; Next Theatre Company, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Coriolanus; William Shakespeare; Festival Theatre (Stratford), 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Coriolanus; William Shakespeare; Shakespeare Theatre Co., 2013 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Country Girl; Clifford Odets; Lyceum Theatre, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cowgirls; Howie, Murfitt; Minetta Lane Theatre, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Creation of the World and Other Business, The; Arthur Miller; Shubert Theatre, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Creeper, The; Pauline Macaulay; Little Theatre Bristol, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Crimes of the Heart; Beth Henley; John Golden Theatre, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Crimes of the Heart; Beth Henley; John Golden Theatre, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Critic / Shewing-Up of Blanco Posnet; Theatre Royal Bristol, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Crucifer of Blood; Paul Giovanni; Helen Hayes Theatre, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time; Simon Stephens; Ethel Barrymore Theatre, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cyrano de Bergerac; Edmond Rostand; Theatre Royal Bristol, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cyrano de Bergerac; Edmond Rostand; Gershwin Theatre, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cyrano de Bergerac; Edmond Rostand; Festival Theatre (Stratford), 2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Da; Hugh Leonard; Morosco Theatre, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dame Kobold; Pedro Calderon; Schiller Theater, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Damsels of Distress: An Ayckbourn Trilogy; Alan Ayckbourn; Duchess Theatre, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dance of Death; August Strindberg; Broadhurst Theatre, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dancing at Lughnasa; Brian Friel; Plymouth Theatre, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Day Room, The; Don DeLillo; Phoenix Theatre, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dear Evan Hansen; Levenson, Pasek, Paul; Music Box, 2019 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Death of a Salesman; Arthur Miller; Nixon Theatre, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Death of Bessie Smith / The American Dream; Edward Albee; Cherry Lane Theatre, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Delicate Balance, A; Edward Albee; Martin Beck Theatre, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Delicate Balance, A; Edward Albee; Arena Stage, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Democracy; Michael Frayn; Brooks Atkinson Theatre, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Design for Living; Noel Coward; Royal George Theatre, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Detective Story; Sidney Kingsley; Festival Theatre (Niagara), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Devils, The; John Whiting; Broadway Theatre, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Devil's Disciple, The; George Bernard Shaw; Festival Theatre (Niagara), 2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Devil's General, The; Carl Zuckmayer; Frankfurt Main Schauspiel, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Diary of a Madman; Nikolai Gogol; Theatre de Brakke Grond, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Diavolo; Jacques Heim; IU Auditorium, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dinner with Friends; Donald Marquiles; Laura Pels Theatre, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dinner with the Family; Jean Anouilh; Little Theatre Bristol, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dirty Rotten Scoundrels; Lane, Yazbek; IU Auditorium, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dividing the Estate; Horton Foote; Booth Theatre, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Doctor's Joy; Moliere; Theatre Royal Bristol, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Don't Dress for Dinner; Marc Camoletti; Duchess Theatre, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Doubt; John Patrick Shanley; N.Y. City Center Stage 1, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Doubt; John Patrick Shanley; Walter Kerr Theatre, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Doubt; John Patrick Shanley; Cardinal Stage Company, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Drawer Boy, The; Michael Healey; Thousand Islands Playhouse, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dresser, The; Ronald Harwood; Queen's Theatre, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Driving Miss Daisy; Alfred Uhry; Briar Street Theatre, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Driving Miss Daisy; Alfred Uhry; J. Howard Wood Theatre, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Driving Miss Daisy; Alfred Uhry; Golden Theatre, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Drowsy Chaperone; Lambert, Martin, etc.; IU Auditorium, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Duchess of Malfi, The; John Webster; Lyttelton Theatre, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Duchess of Malfi, The; John Webster; Wyndham's Theatre, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Duchess of Malfi, The; John Webste; Tom Patterson Theatre, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Duel of Angels; Jean Giraudoux; Apollo Theatre, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Duenna, The; Richard Brinsley; Birmingham Repertory Theatre, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Duet for One; Tom Kempinski; Duke of York's Theatre, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Easy Virtue; Noel Coward; Garrick, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Educating Rita; Willy Russell; Piccadilly Theatre, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Edward IV; William Shakespeare; Wurttembergishche Staatth'r, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Egg, The [Das Ei]; Felicien Marceau; Kammerspiele, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Eh?; Henry Livings; Studio Theater Brakke Grond, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Eighty in the Shade; Clemence Dane; Globe Theatre Shafesbury, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Elder Stateman, The; T.S. Eliot; Cambridge Theatre, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Elephant Man, The; Bernard Pomerance; Booth Theatre, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Enemy of the People, An; Henrik Ibsen; Broadhurst Theatre, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Enemy of the People, An; Henrik Ibsen; The Playhouse, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Enjoy; Alan Bennett; Vaudeville Theatre, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Entertainer, The; John Osborne; Theatre Royal Bristol, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Epic Proportions; Coen, Crane; Helen Hayes Theatre, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Equus; Peter Shaffer; Plymouth Theatre, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Eventyr Paa Fodrejsen; C. Hostrup; Det Kongelige Teater, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Every Brilliant Thing; Jonny Donahoe; Barrow Street Theatre, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Evita; Weber, Rice; Prince Edward Theatre, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Fair Liberty's Call; Sharon Pollock; Tom Patterson Theatre, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fallen Angels; Noel Coward; Apollo Theatre, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fantasticks, The; Tom Jones; Sullivan Street Playhouse, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Far Country, A; Henry Denker; Orpheus (Minneapolis), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Farinelli and the King; Claire Van Kampen; Belasco Theatre, 2018 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fat Pig; Neil LaBute; Lucille Lortel Theatre, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fatal Attraction; Bernard Slade; Theatre Royal Haymarket, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fences; August Wilson; 46th Street Theatre, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Ferryman, The; Jez Butterworth; Bernard B. Jacobs Theatre, 2019 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fiddler on the Roof; Stein, Bock, Harnick; Orpheum (Minneapolis), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Fifth of July; Lanford Wilson; New Apollo Theatre, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Filumena; Eduardo de Filippo; Piccadilly Theatre, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Finian's Rainbow; Lane, Harburg, Saidy; St. James Theatre, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Fiorello; Wiedman, Abbott, Bock; Orpheum (Minneapolis), 1961 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Five Finger Exercise; Peter Shaffer; Comedy Theatre, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Flea in Her Ear, A; Georges Feydeau; National Theatre, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Flight Path; Norm Foster; Thousand Islands Playhouse, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Florida; Marcia Cebulska; Phoenix Theatre, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Flowering Cherry; Robert Bolt; Theatre Royal Haymarket, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Floyd Collins; Guettel, Landau; Court House Theatre (Niagara), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Follies; Stephen Sondheim; Marquis Theatre, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Foreigner, The; Larry Shue; Astor Place Theatre, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Foreigner, The; Larry Shue; Florida Repertory Theatre, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Forest, The; Robert Wilson; Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 40 Years On; Alan Bennet; Apollo Theatre, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Forvandlad till Brudgum; Allan Gergstrand; Marsyas Theatern, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Fosse; Verdon, Reinking, Walker; Broadhurst Theatre, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Four Dogs and a Bone; John Patrick Shanley; Lucille Lortel Theatre, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Fourposter, The; Jan de Hartog; Schlosstheater Celle, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Frankie and Johnny in the Clair de Lune; Terrence McNally; Belasco Theatre, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Freud's Last Session; Mark St. Germain; New World Stages, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Front Page, The; Hecht, MacArthur; Broadhurst Theatre, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Frozen; Bryony Lavery; Studio Theatre Secondstage, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Full Monty, The; MacNally, Yazbek; Eugene O'Neill Theatre, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Gentleman's Guide to Love, A; Freedman, Lutvak; Walter Kerr Theatre, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Ghost Brothers of Darkland County; King, Mellencamp; IU Auditorium, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Giant; LaChiusa, Pearson; Signature Theatre, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Gideon; Paddy Chayefsky; Plymouth Theatre, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Gin Game, The; D.L. Coburn; John Golden Theatre, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Gin Game, The; D.L. Coburn; Avon Theatre, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Give Me Your Answer, Do!; Brian Friel; Gramercy Theatre, 1999; 2 Copies (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Glass Menagerie, The; Tennessee Williams; Comedy Theatre, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Glass Menagerie, The; Tennessee Williams; Booth Theatre, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Glengarry Glen Ross; David Mamet; John Golden Theatre, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Glengarry Glen Ross; David Mamet; Gerald Schoenfeld Theatre, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Goat or Who is Sylvia?; Edward Albee; John Golden Theatre, 2002; 2 Copies (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - God Bless You, Mr. Rosewater; Ashman, Menken; Arena Stage, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - God Bless You, Mr. Rosewater; Ashman, Menken; Phoenix Theatre, 2018 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - God of Carnage; Yasmina Reza; Bernard B. Jacobs Theatre, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Grab Me a Gondola; Moore, Gilbert; Bristol Hippodrome, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Grace; Craig Wright; Cort Theatre, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Grand Hotel; Davis, Wright, Forrest; Martin Beck Theatre, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Grapes of Wrath; Frank Galati; Cardinal Stage Company, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Grass is Greener, The; Hugh, Margaret Williams; St. Martin's Theatre, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Great Sebastians, The; Lindsay, Crouse; Coronet Theatre, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Great White Hope, The; Howard Sackler; Alvin Theatre, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Gross Indecency; Moises Kaufman; Minetta Lane Theatre, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Gross Indecency; Moises Kaufman; Mark Taper Forum, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Guys and Dolls; Loesser, Burrows; Festival Theatre (Stratford), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Hadrian VII; Peter Luke; Helen Hayes Theatre, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Hair; Ragni, Rado, MacDermot; Shaftesbury Theatre, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hairspray; O'Donnell, Shaiman; IU Auditorium, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Half a Sixpence; Cross, Heneker; Broadhurst Theatre, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hamilton; Lin-Manuel Miranda; Murat Theatre, 2019 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hamlet; William Shakespeare; Tyrone Guthrie Theatre, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hamlet; William Shakespeare; Lunt-Fontanne Theatre, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hamlet; William Shakespeare; Indiana Repertory Theatre, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hamlet; William Shakespeare; Lyttelton Theatre, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Harlequinade; Terence Rattigan; Festival Theatre (Niagara), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hapgood; Tom Stoppard; Mitzie E. Newhouse Theatre, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Harper Regan; Simon Stephens; Linda Gross, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Harvey; Mary Chase; National Tour, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Hatful of Rain, A; Michael V. Gazzo; Library Theatre, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Having Our Say; Emily Mann; Cardinal Stage Company, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 29)